# ANDERS GRØN

#### March 2020

Location: 2300 Copenhagen S, Denmark

Contact: (+45) 61 28 32 10 ♦ anders.barslund.green@gmail.com

#### PERSONAL

My goal is to work for an organization which provides me the opportunity to improve my skills and knowledge within public leadership, social innovation, research, and data science. Check out my personal website for more information.

#### **EDUCATION**

Aarhus University

MSc in Political Science

St.Gallen University

Sept. 2017 - Feb. 2020

GPA: 3.8/4.0

Stummer 2019

Summer school, Econometrics of Big Data Grade: none

Essex University
Summer school, Machine Learning for Social Scientists
Summer 2018
Grade: 93/100

London School of Economics Summer 2018

Summer school, Big Data: Data Analytics for Business and Beyond Grade: A

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# PhD Fellow in Political Science

Sept. 2020 - present

Crown Prince Frederik Center for Public Leadership, Aarhus University

Responsible for planning and executing a project focusing on collaborative public leadership. See below.

#### Data Analyst, Machine Learner

Feb. 2018 - July 2020

Rockwool Foundation, Copenhagen

Responsible for planning and executing data analytic work in relation to scoping, developing, and evaluating real-life RCT-based interventions ranging from basic descriptive statistics and graphing to advanced machine learning. Improved analytic, programming, and project facilitation competencies.

#### Teaching Assistant

June 2016 - June 2019

Aarhus BSS, Aarhus

Taught for five semesters in four different subjects. Improved pedagogical and structuring competencies.

# PHD PROJECT

### Project description: Teamwork makes the Dream work?

Description will follow. Description will follow.

## OTHER PROJECTS

Data Science

July 2017 - present

Since July 2017 I have studied data science, statistical learning, and machine learning extensively in both classes, online courses, and my spare time. I am well-versed in different supervised and unsupervised algorithms and I am able to implement them in R and Python. I have composed this report (opens in PDF) on how it is possible to use machine learning in social innovation.

MicroMasters in Data Science (Edx.org)

August 2020 - present

Description will follow.

Author: www.abgroen.com

March 2020 - present

Podcaster and writer at my personal website.

#### OTHER COMPETENCIES

#### **Technical**

Modeling, Data Analysis STATA, R, Python Other tools MS Office, Latex

## Languages

**Danish** Mother tongue

**English** Fluent

German Conversational

PUBLICATIONS
Will be updated.
win be apaated.
COURSES, SEMINARS, CONFERENCES, ETC.
Will be updated.
OTHER

Will be updated.